Disgust is a universal human emotion.
厌恶是人类普遍具有的一种情绪。
One type of disgust is called physical disgust, which protects us from eating or touching things that could be dangerous for us, such as raw meat or insects.
有一种厌恶叫作生理厌恶，它保护我们，使我们不去吃或触碰可能对我们有危险的东西，比如生肉或昆虫。
Children experience physical disgust from a very early age, but do not achieve an understanding of the concept until they are around four years old.
孩子很小的时候就会体验到生理厌恶，但要到四岁左右才能理解这个概念。
Some researchers maintain that there is another type of disgust, called moral disgust, that protects us from engaging in activities that can be perceived as morally wrong.
一些研究者坚持认为还存在另一种厌恶，叫作道德厌恶，它保护我们，使我们不去从事那些可能被视为道德上错误的活动。
Examples of things that cause moral disgust are stealing, lying or cheating.
会引起道德厌恶的事情有偷窃、撒谎、作弊等。
However, not all academics think that moral disgust really exists.
然而，并非所有学者都认为道德厌恶真的存在。
Some say that when we refer to disgust in relation to moral issues, we are using disgust as a metaphor, and what we are feeling is in reality anger.
有些人说，我们在道德问题上说到厌恶时，是把厌恶当作一种比喻来用，实际感受到的是愤怒。
If moral disgust appears quite late in development, it makes sense to think that there is actually a social component to it.
如果道德厌恶在成长过程中出现得相当晚，那么认为它其实带有社会性成分也就合乎情理了。
Children learn about emotions in many different ways.
孩子通过许多不同的途径了解情绪。
Of special relevance are parent-child conversations about emotions.
与此尤为相关的，是父母与孩子之间围绕情绪展开的对话。
Indeed, children whose parents talk about emotions often have a better emotional understanding than children whose parents do not discuss emotions often.
事实上，父母经常谈论情绪的孩子，比父母不常讨论情绪的孩子对情绪理解得更好。
However, there are no studies that have examined how parents and children talk about disgust.
然而，还没有研究考察过父母和孩子是如何谈论厌恶的。
This is what we set out to examine in our study.
这正是我们在研究中着手考察的问题。
We asked 68 English-speaking mothers and their four-, six-, or eight-year-old children to discuss some stories about moral and physical disgust.
我们请68位说英语的母亲和她们四岁、六岁或八岁的孩子讨论一些关于道德厌恶和生理厌恶的故事。
Our preliminary findings show mothers and children do talk about disgust, but mainly about physical disgust and not so much about moral disgust.
我们的初步研究结果显示，母亲和孩子确实会谈论厌恶，但主要谈的是生理厌恶，而不太谈道德厌恶。
When we asked mothers and children to discuss moral issues, such as whether it is OK to play with a child who has stolen someone else’s snack, they linked this type of moral wrongdoing with the emotion of anger and not disgust.
我们让母亲和孩子讨论道德问题，比如可不可以和一个偷了别人零食的孩子一起玩，这时他们把这类道德上的错误行为与愤怒这种情绪联系在一起，而不是与厌恶联系在一起。
Does this mean that moral disgust does not exist?
这是否意味着道德厌恶并不存在？
Some researchers suggest moral disgust exists in adults.
一些研究者认为，成年人身上存在道德厌恶。
Our findings suggest that moral disgust is either understood at a later age or only used metaphorically, if at all, in children as old as eight years.
我们的研究结果表明，对八岁及以下的孩子来说，道德厌恶要么要到年龄更大些才能理解，要么即便用到，也只是作比喻用。